ACTWU's Department of Occupational Safety and Health Records 5619/015
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Capitol Plastics of Ohio, Inc., Bowling Green, OH (Box 64, Folder 9)
- OSH Case Capitol Dye Works, Inc. New York, New York, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- Carporale Engraving Co., Hackensack, NJ (Box 64, Folder 10)
- OSH Case Capitol Plastics of Ohio, Inc. Bowling Green, Ohio, 1979-1981 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Capri Textile Processor Inc., Fall River, MA (Box 64, Folder 11)
- OSH Case Caporale Engraving Company, Inc. Hackensack, New Jersey, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Carborundum Co., (Commercial Filters Div.) (Box 64, Folder 12)
- OSH Case Capri Textile Processors, Inc. Fall River, Massachusetts, 1982-1983 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Cardinal Shoes, Lawrence, MA (Box 64, Folder 13)
- OSHA Case Carborundum Company (Commercial Filters Div.) Tell City, Indiana, 1972-1982 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Carnegie Coating Co. (Box 64, Folder 14)
- OSH Case Carlisle Corporation Geauga Co., 1981 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- Carroll Shoe, Co., Summerville, WV. (Box 64, Folder 15)
- OSH Case Carnegie Coating Company, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Carville, Inc. Gloversville/Johnstown, NY (Box 64, Folder 16)
- OSH Case Carroll Shoe Company Summersville, West Virginia 26651, 1980-1981 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Cascade Laundry, Brooklyn, NY (Box 64, Folder 17)
- OSH Case Carville, Inc. Gloversville/Johnstown, New York, 1984-1988 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Cayadutta Tanning Co., Inc., Gloversville, NY (Box 64, Folder 18)
- OSH Case Cascade Laundry, Brooklyn, New York, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Central Coat and Apron Co., NY, NY (Box 64, Folder 19)
- OSH Case Cayadutta Tanning Company, Inc. Gloversville, New York, 1975-1978 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Central Counter Co., St. Louis, MO (Box 64, Folder 20)
- OSH Case Central Coat and Apron Company, Manhattan, New York, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Centre Finishing Corp., NY, NY (Box 64, Folder 21)
- OSH Case Central Counter Company, St. Louis, Missouri, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Champion Dyeing and Finishing, Paterson, NJ (Box 64, Folder 22)
- OSH Case Centre Finishing Corporation, New York, New York, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Champion International, Frenchtown, MT (Box 64, Folder 23)
- OSH Case Champion Dyeing and Finishing, Paterson, New Jersey, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Channel Mills, Bradford, VT (Box 64, Folder 24)
- OSH Case Champion International, Frenchtown, MT, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Charleswood Furniture, Wright City, MO (Formerly St. Charles Furniture) (Box 64, Folder 25)
- OSH Case Channel Mills, Bradford, Vermont, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- Chase Bag Co. (Box 64, Folder 26)
- OSH Case Charleswood Furniture, Wright City, Missouri (formerly St. Charles Furniture), 1978-1991 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Chatham Mfg. Co., Chicopee, MA (Box 64, Folder 27)
- OSH Case Chase Bag Company, 1983-1987 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Chromatex, Inc., Hazelton, PA (Box 64, Folder 28)
- OSHA Case Chatham Manufacturing Company, Elkin, North Carolina, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 28)
- City Shirt Co., Frackville, PA (Box 64, Folder 29)
- OSH Case Chenro Company, Fredonia, Wisconsin, 1986 (Box 64, Folder 29)
- Cindus Corp., Cincinnati, OH (Box 64, Folder 30)
- OSHA Case Chicopee Manufacturing Company, Chicopee, Massachusetts, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 30)
- Cintas Corp., Pico Rivera, CA (Box 64, Folder 31)
- OSH Case Chromatex, Inc. Hazelton, Pennsylvania, 1981-1987 (Box 64, Folder 31)
- Clark, Cutler, McDermott, Franklin, MA (Box 64, Folder 32)
- OSH Case City Shirt Company, Frackville, Pennsylvania, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 32)
  Cloth
- Classy Togs, NYC (Box 64, Folder 33)
- OSH Case Cindus Corporation, Cincinnati, Ohio, 1981-1985 (Box 64, Folder 33)
- Clifton Yarn Mills, Inc., Clifton Heights, PA (Box 64, Folder 34)
- OSH Case Cintas Corporation Pico Rivera, California, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 34)
- Clifton Yarn Mills, Inc., Phil. PA (Box 64, Folder 35)
- OSH Case Clark, Cutler, McDermott, Franklin, Massachusetts, 1980-1984 (Box 64, Folder 35)
- Cliftex Mfg., New Bedford, MA (Box 64, Folder 36)
- OSH Case Classy Togs, New York, New York, 1982 (Box 64, Folder 36)
- Cluett Peabody Co., Enterprise, AL (Box 64, Folder 37)
- OSH Case Clifton Yarn Mills, Inc. Clifton Heights, Pennsylvania, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 37)
- Cobbs Industries, Trenton, NJ (Box 64, Folder 38)
- OSH Case Clifton Yarn Mills, Inc. Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 38)
- Cobe Laboratories Inc., Denver, Colorado (Box 64, Folder 39)
- OSH Case Cluett-Peabody Company, Inc. Enterprise, Alabama 36330, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 39)
- Cohoes Fabrics Printers, Inc. Cohoes, NY (Box 64, Folder 40)
- OSH Case Cobbs Industries, Trenton, New Jersey, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 40)
- Colecraft Mfg. Co., Inc., Lancaster, NY (Box 64, Folder 41)
- OSH Case Cobe Laboratories, Inc. Denver, Colorado, 1988 (Box 64, Folder 41)
- College House Mfg., Inc., Westbury, NY (Box 64, Folder 42)
- OSH Case Cohoes Fabrics Printers, Inc. Cohoes, New York, 1983-1987 (Box 64, Folder 42)
- Colonial Printing Inc., Co., E. Rutherford, NJ (Box 64, Folder 43)
- OSH Case Colecraft Manufacturing Company, Inc. Lancaster, New York, 1980-1990 (Box 64, Folder 43)
- Colonial Tanning (Box 64, Folder 44)
- OSH Case College House Manufacturing, Inc. Westbury, New York, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 44)
- Colt Enterprise Inc., Tyler, TX (Box 64, Folder 45)
- OSH Case Colonial Printing Ink Company, East Rutherford, New Jersey, 1981-1983 (Box 64, Folder 45)
- Columbian Rope Co., Auburn, NY (Box 64, Folder 46)
- OSH Case Colonial Tanning, 1983-1988 (Box 64, Folder 46)
- Columbus Coated Fabric, Columbus, OH, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 47)
- OSH Case Colt Enterprises, Inc. Tyler, Texas, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 47)
- OSHA Case Columbian Rope Company, Auburn, New York, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 48)
- OSHA Case Columbus Coated Fabrics (Division of Borden Company) Columbus, Ohio, 1973 (Box 64, Folder 49)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department Enforcement, 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department Department Enforcement, 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 1)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department VI Enforcement, 1983-1985 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- OSH Administration Labor Department Enforcement, 1983-1987 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department General, 1977-979 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department I General, 1977-1979 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department, 1980-1982 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- OSH Administration Labor Department I General, 1979-1984 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department Joint Committee (Box 65, Folder 5)
- OSH Administration of Law (XI) Labor Department-Joint Committee, 1981-1982 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department IIA Record Keeping 1980 Access Standard (Box 65, Folder 6)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department IIA Recordkeeping Access Standard, 1978-1980 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department III Std., 1975-1976 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department 11A Recordkeeping Access Standard, 1979-1983 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department III Standards, 1975-1981 (Box 65, Folder 8)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department - III - Standards, 1976-1982 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Administration of Law Labor Department (III) Standards, 1981-1984 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department III Std., 1977-1982 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department (III) Standards, 1981-1984 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department III Std., 1982-1984 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department (III) Standards, 1985-1990 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department III Std., 1985 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- OSH Administration of Law Labor Department IV Target Health Hazards Program., 1972-1974 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- OSH ADMIN. Labor Department IV Target Health Hazard Program 1972 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- OSH Administration of Law NIOSH, 1977-1980 (Box 66, Folder 4)
- OSH ADMIN. NIOSH, 1977-1980 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- OSH Administration NIOSH - High Risk Lobbying, 1985-1988 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- OSH ADMIN. NIOSH - High Risk Lobbying (Box 66, Folder 6)
- OSH Administration of Law State Plans North Carolina, 1978-1982 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- OSH ADMIN. State Plans - NC, 1978 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- OSH ACTWU Activities Convention 1981, 1981-1989 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- ACTWU ACTIVITIES. Convention, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- OSH ACTWU Occupational Health Hazards Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- ACTWU ACTIVITIES. Occupational Health Hazard Comm. (Box 66, Folder 9)
- OSH ACTWU Activities (other than U.S. Hearings, Executive Committee, 1969-1982 (Box 66, Folder 9)
- ACTWU ACTIVITIES. Other than U.S. Hearings Exec. Comm. (Box 66, Folder 10)
- OSH ACTWU Activities Single Pants, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 10)
- ACTWU ACTIVITIES. Single Pants (Box 66, Folder 11)
- ACTWU. Exec. Council Committee (Box 67, Folder 1)
- OSH ACTWU Distributions, 1971-1987 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- ACTWU. Local Union Committee (Box 67, Folder 2)
- OSH ACTWU Executive Council Committee, 1970-1974 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- ACTWU. Referral to Doctors (Box 67, Folder 3)
- OSH ACTWU Local Union Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- ACTWU. Surveys & Misc., 1971-1972 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- OSH ACTWU Referrals to Doctors, 1971-1983 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- ACTWU. TWUA Health Plan (Box 67, Folder 5)
- OSH ACTWU Surveys and Misc., 1970-1976 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- ACTWU. TWUA Pension Fund (Box 67, Folder 6)
- OSH ACTWU TWUA Health Plan, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- OSH ADMIN. Appropriations, 1971-1984 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- OSH ACTWU TWUA Pension Fund, 1982-1984 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- OSH ADMIN BLS. Recordkeeping Guidelines, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- OSH Administration of Law Appropriations, 1971-1982 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- OSH ADMIN BLS. Quality Assurance Program (Box 67, Folder 9)
- OSH Administration of Law Appropriations, 1974-1984 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- OSH ADMIN BLS. LRAC, 1985 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- OSH Administration BLS Recordkeeping Guidelines, 1982-1985 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- OSH Administration BLS Recordkeeping Guidelines, 1983-1987 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- OSH Administration BLS Quality Assurance Program, 1984-1988 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- OSH Administration BLS - LRAC ( Labor Research Advisory Committee, 1984-1986 (Box 67, Folder 13)
- OSH Administration BLS - LRAC (Labor Research Advisory Committee), 1981-1984 (Box 67, Folder 14)
- Congress Attacks, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- OSH Administration of Law Congressional Attacks, 1980-1981 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- Congressional Oversight, 1983-1987 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- OSH Administration of Law Congressional Oversight Proposed Legislation, 1979-1981 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Congressional Oversight Comm., 1981 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- OSH Administration Congressional, 1983-1987 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Congressional Oversight, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- OSH Administration of Law Congressional Oversight Committee, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- Congressional Oversight Proposed Legislation., 1980 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- OSH Administration of Law Congressional Oversight, 1979-1982 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- OSH Files. AFL-CIO. NY State (Box 68, Folder 6)
- OSH AFL-CIO New York State, 1985-1990 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- OSH Files. AFL-CIO. Staff Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- AFL-CIO Staff Committee, 1984-1988 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- OSH Files. AFL-CIO. III Committee on OSHA, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- OSH AFL-CIO III Committee of OSHA, 1982-1986 (Box 68, Folder 8)
- OSH Files. AFL-CIO. Conference, 1984 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- OSH AFL-CIO Conference, 1984-1985 (Box 68, Folder 9)
- OSH Files. AFL-CIO. VI National Conference, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- OSH AFL-CIO VI National Conference, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 10)
- ANSI (American National Standard Institute) (Box 68, Folder 11)
- OSH American National Standards Institute, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- Canada (Box 69, Folder 1)
- OSHA Canada, 1978-1985 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Chicago Area Committee on Occupational Safety and Health (Box 69, Folder 2)
- OSHA Chicago Area Committee on Occupational Safety and health, 1975-1982 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- Coalition for Reproductive Rights of Workers (Box 69, Folder 3)
- OSH Coal Mine Safety Acts, 1969-1984 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Coal Mine Safety Acts (Box 69, Folder 4)
- OSH Colate, 1981 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Colate (Box 69, Folder 5)
- OSHA Companies, 1970-1985 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Companies (Box 69, Folder 6)
- OSHA Industrial Relations Research Association, 1972 (Box 69, Folder 6)
- Industrial Relations Research Assoc., 1972 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- OSHA Inflationary Impact Statement, 1977 (Box 69, Folder 7)
- Inflationary Impact Statement (Box 69, Folder 8)
- OSHA Interagency Task Force on Workplace Safety and Health, 1978-1979 (Box 69, Folder 8)
- International. Citizens Commission on Bhopal (Box 69, Folder 9)
- OSH International Citizens Commission on Bhopal, 1985-1991 (Box 69, Folder 9)
- International. Standards thru 1984 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- OSHA International Standards, 1976-1984 (Box 69, Folder 10)
- International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers Federation thru 1988 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- OSH International Textile, Garment and Leather Workers' Federation, 1984-1988 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- John Hopkins University Assoc. (Box 69, Folder 12)
- OSH The Johns Hopkins University Associates, 1983-1984 (Box 69, Folder 12)
- Byssinosis ACTWU Activities (other than Research Project, etc), 1969-1986 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis ACTWU Activities Protest, May 4, 1981, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis ACTWU Distribution, 1980-1983 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Byss American Chemical Society, 1984 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis Carolina Brown Lung Association IV: 1979, 1978-1984 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis Center for Study of Responsive Law, 1970-1981 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis Conferences American Chemical Society Atlanta, Georgia, 1980-1981 (Box 70, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis Conference on U.N.C., 1970-1971 (Box 70, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis Conference, Winston-Salem, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis Cotton Dust Conference, 1980 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis Cotton Dust Conference Charlotte, North Carolina, 1979-1981 (Box 71, Folder 1)
- Byssinosis Dan River, Colorado, 1980-1985 (Box 71, Folder 2)
- Byssinosis Dan River Clippings, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Byssinosis Duke University, 1971-1973 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Byssinosis Industrial Health Foundation Study, 1968-1973 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis Variance App. II Bouhuys, 1972 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- Byssinosis Variance App. III Co. Correspondence., 1972-1973 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Byssinosis Variance App. IV Burlington, 1970-1973 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- Byssinosis Walsh-Healy Act, 1969-1978 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Byssinosis Waste Cotton, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- Byssinosis Waste Processing Industry, 1981-1983 (Box 71, Folder 11)
- Byssinosis Weill, Hans, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 12)
- Byssinosis Work Practices, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 13)
- Byssinosis World Health Organization, 1982-1983 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Industrial Memoranda Book#1 Section II Occupational Safety and Health (Box 72, Folder 1)
  Book
- Industry Memoranda Book #2 Section 11 Occupational Safety and Health (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee TWUA Statement, 1972-1973 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Comm. Medico Legal Consid. (Hueper), 1973 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Economics Aspects of OSH Standard for Use of Fourteen Carcinogenic Compounds, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Literature, 1974-1976 (Box 73, Folder 4)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee IUD Committee, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 5)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Correspondence (Misc.), 1973 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Miscellaneous, 1973-1975 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Labor Department - Administration, Procedures, etc., 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Labor Department - Rules, Regulations, 1973-1976 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee NIOSH, 1972-1976 (Box 73, Folder 10)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Health Research Group and OCAW Petition, Etc., 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Industry Comments, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Carcinogens Advisory Committee OSHA, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Proposed Standard, 1973 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Carcinogens, Standard Advisory Committee Labor Department Proposed Standard Impact State, 1973-1974 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Tech Data (NIH-NCL), 1973 (Box 73, Folder 16)
- Field Surveys (NIOSH), 1972-1973 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Inter Office Memos TWUA General, 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 1)
- Interoffice Memos TWUA General, 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Interoffice Memos TWUA General Pres., 1974-1976 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Interoffice Memos TWUA General Pres., 1975 (Box 74, Folder 4)
- Interoffice Memos TWUA General Pres., 1974-1975 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Interoffice Memos Staff, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Interoffice Memos General Offices, 1980 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Interoffice Memos General Offices, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 9)
- Interoffice Memos Staff, 1981-1989 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Interoffice Memos Staff, 1981-1983 (Box 74, Folder 11)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1979-1983 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1983-1986 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1982-1986 (Box 74, Folder 16)
- Interoffice Memos General Officers, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 17)
- Centaur Report to OSHA - The Cotton Dust Standard Volume II Appendices, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 1)
- United States Department of Labor OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 2)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 3)
  Court Documents
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 4)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Docket Number H-052E, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 5)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Informal Public Hearing Docket Number H-052-E, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Informal Public Hearing, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 6)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Informal Public Hearing, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 7)
- OSHA Occupational exposure to Cotton Dust Informal Public Hearing, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 8)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Docket Number H-052E, 1983 (Box 75, Folder 9)
- IHF/ATMI Textile Mill Respiratory Research, 1972 (Box 76, Folder 1)
- Cotton Dust Proceedings of a Topical Symposium, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 2)
- Cotton Dust Controls in Yarn Manufacturing, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 3)
- NIOSH Evaluation of Cotton Dust Control Systems, 1978 (Box 76, Folder 4)
- Cotton Dust Volume 1 Inflationary Impact Statement, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 5)
- Cotton Dust Volume 2 Inflationary Impact Statement, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 6)
- Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Recommended Standard, 1974 (Box 76, Folder 7)
- Engineering Control and Monitoring of Cotton Dust, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 8)
- Carolina Cotton Dust "Warning Sign" Standard Hearing, 1975 (Box 76, Folder 9)
- North Carolina Department of Labor OSHA Occupational Health Guide for Cotton Dust, 1973 (Box 76, Folder 10)
- Textile Industry Study, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 11)
- Textile Industry Study, 1976 (Box 76, Folder 12)
- Congress Report Cotton Dust: Alternative Technical Standards and Control Technologies, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 13)
- Report to Congress Cotton Dust: Review of Alternative Technical Standards and Control Technologies, 1979 (Box 76, Folder 14)
- Control Technology Assessment of Raw Cotton Processing Operations, 1980 (Box 76, Folder 15)
- Technical and Economic Analysis of Regulating Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 16)
- Centaur Report to OSHA The Cotton Dust Standard Volume I Chapters 1-7, 1983 (Box 76, Folder 17)
- ACTWU Testimony, 1975-1977 (Box 77, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Position, 1974-1977 (Box 77, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Industries, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 3)
- ATMI, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 4)
- Cotton Dust Sampling for All Plants, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 5)
- Byssinosis, 1975-1977 (Box 77, Folder 6)
- Clippings, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 7)
- Consultants, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 8)
- Dust Sampling, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 9)
- Hearing Notices of Intent to Appear, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 10)
- Health Res Grp., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- Hearing - Written Statement and Comments, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 12)
- Inflation Impact Statement, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 13)
- Investa, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 14)
- Literature Search, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 15)
- Medical Surveillance, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 16)
- NIOSH, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 17)
- North Carolina OSHA, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 18)
- OSHA, 1974-1977 (Box 77, Folder 19)
- Sources for Plant Lists (Box 77, Folder 20)
  No Contents
- Procedural Questions, 1976-1977 (Box 77, Folder 21)
- Respirators - Gen., 1977 (Box 77, Folder 22)
- Respirators - Testimony, 1973-1977 (Box 77, Folder 23)
- Support Groups, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 24)
- Technical Feasibility, 1976 (Box 77, Folder 25)
- UNC, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 26)
- Vendors, 1975 (Box 77, Folder 27)
- Worker Compensation, 1977 (Box 77, Folder 28)
- ACTWU Informal Public Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- OSHA Informal Public Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Reactivity of Employees Exposed to Cotton Dust, 1971-1973 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- OSHA Informal Public Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust Recommended Standard, 1974 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- OSHA Informal Public Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- OSHA Informal Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- OSHA Public Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- OSHA Brown Lung Testimony, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- OSHA Occupational Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- OSHA Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- NIOSH Proposed Standards for Cotton Dust Exposure, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- Byssinosis Testimony, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- Proposed Cotton Dust Exposure Standard, 1976-1977 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- Cotton Dust Volume 1, 1976 (Box 78, Folder 16)
- EX 6 (Articles), 1970-1978 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- ACTWU Volume II Union Statement Proposed Cotton Dust Standard, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Proposed Standards for Cotton Dust Exposure, 1968-1977 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- ACTWU Introductory Statement by Sol Stetin, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Proposed Standards for Cotton Dust Exposure, 1977 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- The Textile Industry Study, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- Supplement: The Textile Industry Study, 1976 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- OSHA Hearing on Proposed Standard for Exposure to Cotton Dust Transcript, 1977 (Box 79, Folder 8)